antarestech.com 2019-12-12

# Privacy Policy - Antares

This Privacy Policy provides details on how we treat your personal information. Antares Audio Technologies, LLC (“Antares,” “we” or “us”), is the Data Controller with respect to information collected on this website, our software products and any mobile applications we may provide, now or in the future.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to websites maintained by other companies or to which we may link.

### Information We Collect and Use

We collect and use personal information about you to establish your user account, and to interact with you to provide customer service. Specifically, when you set up an account with any of our services, we require your e-mail address and first and last name. You will also be asked to provide your phone number and address, which allows us to personalize our services to you; however, this information is optional and not required to establish an account.

We may also collect credit card information in connection with any purchase you may make. Any such information required to process a transaction is collected securely by our credit card processor and we do not have access to your credit card information, other than the last 4 digits of your account number, which we retain for tracking purposes.

At times we receive data from third-party organisations when they have received your consent to share data with third-parties.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

We share personal information about you under the following circumstances:

Credit Card Processing. As mentioned above, we will pass your information securely to our credit card processor, as required. We only use credit card processors that are fully PCI compliant.

Aggregate, Non-Personal, or De-identified Information. We may share aggregated information (i.e., information about you and other users collectively, but not specifically identifiable to you) and other non-personal, de-identified, or anonymous information we collect, with third parties to optimize their ability to reach their target markets.

As Required by Law. We may be required to share your personal information with law enforcement or government agencies in response to subpoenas, court orders, federal/state audits or similar circumstances whenever we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.

Business Transfer. As with any other business, it is possible that we could in the future enter into a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale. If such a transaction occurs, the successor company would have access to the information maintained by us, including your personal information, but would continue to be bound by this Privacy Policy.

### Information Collection Technologies

To better serve our users and to analyze and enhance the performance of our websites and mobile applications, we use cookies and similar technologies to collect information about our users, such as your browsing behavior, links clicked, device type, and to collect various data, including analytics, about how you use and interact with our Sites and our advertisers. We also use third-party cookies from Google and other similar providers for analytics purposes.

To opt-out of the use of cookies on our Sites, you can change your browser options to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting cookies. Certain aspects of our service, such as remembering your user account information or shopping cart contents, may be limited if you do not accept cookies. More information about cookies and other tracking technologies is available at allaboutcookies.org or youronlinechoices.eu.

In connection with the effectiveness of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) in the European Economic Area (EEA), we seek your specific consent before collecting your personal data on our website and, to the extent applicable, our software and mobile applications.

• If you are registering an account, downloading trial version software, or making a purchase with Antares.com for the first time, or the first time after we make a material change, we will seek your consent to use collect your personal data.  
• If you do not consent, you will still be able to use the site, but certain functionality may be limited.

### Emails

By providing your contact information to us, you are registering to receive communications from us directly or through a third-party. If you no longer wish to receive these communications, please let us know by sending an email to [dpo@antarestech.com](mailto:dpo@antarestech.com). You may also opt-out by clicking on the unsubscribe link in our emails. Even if you opt-out, we may still send you notices related to your account or as otherwise required to comply with applicable law or other contractual requirements.

### Third-Party Advertisers

Please note that we only control our own mailing list and policies. Third-party advertisers that maintain their own mailing lists may send communications that advertise our services. You would need to contact these parties directly in order to stop receiving their email communications.

### Confidentiality and Security

The security of your personal information is very important, and we take a number of steps to safeguard it. For example, we limit access to personal information to those employees or agents who need the information to provide requested products and services to you. We also maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with or exceed federal standards to guard your personal information, and we anonymize or expunge data when it is no longer necessary to provide services to our users or substantiate records for our partners.

### Third-Party Links

This Privacy Policy applies to all information that you provide to us. However, when you visit links from our Sites, keep in mind you will be interacting with a third-party that operates under its own privacy and security policy. If you choose to obtain services through a third-party site, the data collected by the third-party is governed by their privacy policy. A third-party site should also have its own policy regarding the use of cookies and other tracking technologies. We encourage you to review the policies of any other service provider from whom you request services.

### A Special Note about Children’s Privacy

You must be at least 18 years old to use this website. We do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personal information about visitors under 18 years of age. If you are under 18 years of age, you can use the services offered on our websites only in conjunction with your parents or guardians. Please see our Terms of Use for more information.

### Updating, Obtaining or Removing Your Information

Upon request via email or mail, we will provide you a summary of personal information retained by us. We will only send your personal records to your email address or postal address that we have on file for you. To obtain, modify, correct, change, update or remove your personal records from our database, please send your request via email to our Data Protection Officer at [dpo@antarestech.com](mailto:dpo@antarestech.com) – note can be same as above if you want]. We will require that you prove your identity before providing any personal information.

### Special Notice to California Residents

California residents may, no more than once per calendar year, request information about our disclosures of certain categories of personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. To be valid, requests must be submitted to us at [dpo@antarestech.com](mailto:dpo@antarestech.com). Within thirty days of receiving this request, we will provide a list of the categories of personal information disclosed for direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, along with the names and addresses of the third parties.

### Visitors outside the United States

This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on our Sites from residents of the United States. The data protection and other laws of the United States might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By visiting our Sites or using our services, you acknowledge and agree that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy, regardless of the laws of your residence country.  
To the extent the laws of another jurisdiction apply to your data or use of the Sites, we will comply with such laws.

### Questions and Suggestions

If you have any questions, concerns or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us by sending an email to: [dpo@antarestech.com](mailto:dpo@antarestech.com).

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. If there are material changes to this Privacy Policy or in how we will use your personal information, we will prominently post notice of such changes on the Sites. However, you should check this Privacy Policy whenever you use any of our Sites to ensure you are aware of our current privacy practices. Our Privacy Policy will indicate the date it was last updated. Your continued use of our Sites after we have posted any changes indicates your agreement to the changes, unless you notify us otherwise.

### Your Agreement

By using this website or our services, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use any portion of our website or services.

##### Updated May 2018
